A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Laboratory Tests - Drugs and Other Factors Affecting Laboratory Tests" 13:20, 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 7-11)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Treatment and Prevention of Syphilis and Gonorrhea" 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 230, Folder 1-7)
- "Gonococcal Infections - The Condom as a Venereal Disease Preventive" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:21, 1971 December 24 (Box 230, Folder 8)
- "Probenecid - Use of Probenecid in Antimicrobial Therapy" 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 231, Folder 1-5)
- "Antimicrobials, Sensitivity - Interpretation of Antimicrobial Susceptibility Tests" 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 6-10)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Glucose) - Reflectance Meter/Dextrostix System for Blood Glucose" 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 11-15)
- "Air Pollution - Cigarette Smoking and Carbon Monoxide" 13:22, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 1-3)
- "Transplantation - Transplantation of Organs Other Than Kidneys" 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 4-8)
- "Antacid - Antacid Therapy for Peptic Ulcer" 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 9, Box 233, Folder 1-5)
- "Vitamins, E - Vitamin E 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 233, Folder 6-10)
- "Nitrofurantotin - Nitrofurantotin" 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 234, Folder 1-7)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 234, Folder 8-12, Box 235, Folder 1-3)
- "Antihistamines - Choice of Antihistamines" 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 4-8)
- "Spectinomycin - Spectinomycin, A New Antibiotic For Genital Gonorrhea" 13:26, 1971 December (Box 235, Folder 9-13)
- "Corticosteroids (Meprednisone) - Meprednisone (Betapar)" 13:106, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 1-6)
- "Flavoxate - Flavoxate Hydrochloride (Urispas) " (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:107, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 7-11)
- "Penicillin Allergy - The Medical Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) Med. Lett., Handbook, 1972 January (Box 236, Folder 12)
- "Penicillin Allergy - The Medical Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy" (Original Manuscript) Med. Lett., Handbook, 1972 January (Box 236, Folder 13)
- "Tetracyclines (Liver Damage) - Doxycycline and Renal Failure" 14:3, 1972 January 7 (Box 236, Folder 14-18)
- "Hypoglycemia - Hypoglycemia in Adults" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 14:7, 1972 February 4 (Box 236, Folder 19)
- "Corticosteroids (Meprednisone) - Meprednisone (Betapar) " (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:106, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 1-6)
- "Flavoxate - Flavoxate Hydrochloride (Urispas) " (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:107, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 7-11)
- "Penicillin Allergy - The Medical Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) Med. Lett., Handbook, 1972 January (Box 236, Folder 12)
- "Penicillin Allergy - The Medical Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy" (Original Manuscript) Med. Lett., Handbook, 1972 January (Box 236, Folder 13)
- "Parenteral Administration - The Medical Letter Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy" Med. Lett., Handbook, 1972 January (Box 236, Folder 14-17, Box 237, Folder 1-4)
- "Diabetes Therapy - (Phenformin) Phenformin and Vascular Complications of Diabetes" 14:1, 1972 January 7 (Box 237, Folder 5-9)
- "Narcotic Antagonist - Naloxone Hydrochloride (Narcan) a new Narcotic Antagonist" 14:2, 1972 January 7 (Box 237, Folder 10-15)
- "Tetracyclines (Liver Damage) - Doxycycline and Renal Failure" 14:3, 1972 January 7 (Box 238, Folder 1-2, Box 237, Folder 16-18)
- Medical Letter (Special Publ.) "The Medical Letter Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy" 14:4, 1972 January 7 (Box 238, Folder 3-7)
- "Lead - Treatment of lead poisoning" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 14:5, 1972 February 4 (Box 238, Folder 8-12, Box 239, Folder 1-2)
- "Hypoglycemia - Hypoglycemia in Adults" 14:7, 1972 February 4 (Box 239, Folder 3-8)
- "Tetracyclines-Minocycline (Minocin)" 14:9, 1972 February 18 (Box 239, Folder 9-11, Box 240, Folder 1-2)
- "Eye - Soft Contact Lenses" 14:10, 1972 February 18 (Box 240, Folder 3-7)
- Medical Letter (Special Publ.) "Prophylactic dose of human tetanus immune globulin" (Final Draft & Handbook) 14:12, 1972 February 18 (Box 240, Folder 8)
- "Methadone - Methadone in the management of heroin addiction" 14:13, 1972 March 3 (Box 240, Folder 7-9, Box 241, Folder 1-3)
- "Clomiphene - Clomiphene" 14:15, 1972 March 3 (Box 241, Folder 4-9)
- "LASERS - Photocoagulation Therapy of Diabetic Retinopathy" 14:6, 1972 March 17 (Box 242, Folder 1-4)
- "Poison and Poisoning - The Management of Lye Burns of the Esophagus", 14:6, 1972 March 17 (Box 242, Folder 5-9)
- "Congenital Malformations - Ambiguous Genitalia", 14:6, 1972 March 17 (Box 242, Folder 10-13)
- "Hyperkinetic Children: Amphetamine-Type Drugs for Hyperactive Children", 14:7, 1972 March 31 (Box 242, Folder 14-15, Box 243, Folder 1-2)
- "Bone: New Drugs for the Treatment of Paget's Disease", 14:7, 1972 March 31 (Box 243, Folder 3-7)
- "Antimicrobial Prophylaxis in Surgery", 14:8, 1972 April 14 (Box 243, Folder 8-11, Box 244, Folder 1-2)
- "Sunburn - Topical Sun Screening Agents", 14:8, 1972 April 14 (Box 244, Folder 3-7)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical - Fluocinonide (Lidex) - Another Topical Steroid", 14:9, 1972 April 28 (Box 244, Folder 8-13)
- "Mefenamic Acid - Mefenamic Acid (Ponstel) Again" 14:9, 1972 April 28 (Box 244, Folder 14)
- "Parasitic Infections: Infectious Diseases from Southeast Asia", 14:10, 1972 May 12 (Box 245, Folder 1-4)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (CNS) - Drugs that Cause Depression", 14:10, 1972 May 12 (Box 246, Folder 1-2, Box 245, Folder 5-8)
- "Dextropropoxyphene - Darvon and Darvon-N." Receipts and Circulating Draft Checklist, 14:11, 1972 May 26 (Box 246, Folder 3)
- "Dextropropoxyphene - Darvon and Darvon-N.", 14:11, 1972 May 26 (Box 246, Folder 4-7)
- "Penicillins, New (Hetacillin) - Advertisements for Hetacillin", 14:11, 1972 May 26 (Box 246, Folder 8-13)
- "Metronidazole (Flagyl) for Amebiasis - A Note on Amebic Liver Abscess", 14:11, 1972 May 26 (Box 246, Folder 14-19)
- "Methotrexate - Methotrexate in the Treatment of Psoriasis", 14:12, 1972 June 9 (Box 247, Folder 1-6)
- "Halothane - Halothane Hepatitis" 14:12, 1972 June 9 (Box 247, Folder 7)
- "Analgesics - Percodan", 14:12, 1972 June 9 (Box 247, Folder 8-13)
- "Rubella - Rubella Vaccination of Women", 14:13, 1972 June 23 (Box 247, Folder 14-15, Box 248, Folder 1-2)
- "Pentazocine - Pentazocine", 14:13, 1972 June 23 (Box 248, Folder 3-9)
- "Topical Gentamicin", 14:13, 1972 June 23 (Box 248, Folder 10-14)
- "Parasitic Infections - Pyrantel Pamoate (Antiminth)", 14:14, 1972 July 7 (Box 248, Folder 15-20)
- "Vitamins (Folic Acid) - Uses of Folic Acid in Pregnancy and in Clinical Disorders", 14:14, 1972 July 7 (Box 248, Folder 21, Box 249, Folder 1-5)
- "Amniocentesis - Diagnostic Amniocentesis", 14:15, 1972 July 21 (Box 249, Folder 6-9)
- "Soaps and Detergents - Soaps and Cleansers", 14:15, 1972 July 21 (Box 249, Folder 10-15)
- "Achlorhydria: Hydrochloric Acid Therapy", 14:15, 1972 July 21 (Box 250, Folder 1-3)
- "Malaria - 8/72", 1972 (Box 250, Folder 4-8)
- "Polio Vaccine (New) - Diplovax - A New Oral Polio Vaccine", 14:16, 1972 August 4 (Box 250, Folder 9-15)
- "Diagnostic Tests - Rheumatoid Factor Tests", 14:16, 1972 August 4 (Box 250, Folder 16-20, Box 251, Folder 1)
- "Lactobacillus - Bacid, Lactinex, and Yogurt", 14:16, 1972 August 4 (Box 251, Folder 2-7)
- "Diuretics: Furosemide", 14:17, 1972 August 18 (Box 251, Folder 8-11, Box 252, Folder 1-2)
- "Oral Contraceptives and Thromboembolism", 14:17, 1972 August 18 (Box 252, Folder 3-8)
- "Chinese Drugs - Notes on Drugs and Therapeutics in the People's Republic of China", 14:18, 1972 September 1 (Box 253, Folder 1-5)
- "Plastics - Viaflex Containers", 14:19, 1972 September 15 (Box 253, Folder 6-12)
- "Tuberculin - Tuberculin Tests", 14:19, 1972 September 15 (Box 254, Folder 1-7)
- "Sarcoidosis - Sarcoidosis and the Kveim Test", 14:19, 1972 September 15 (Box 254, Folder 8-12)
- "Ketamine Hydrochloride: A Second Look", 14:20, 1972 September 29 (Box 254, Folder 13-17)
- "Nutrition and Diet (Parenteral) - Total Intravenous Feeding", 14:20, 1972 September 29 (Box 255, Folder 1-5)
- "Hypnotics and Sedatives - Triclofos Sodium (Triclos) for Insomnia", 14:21, 1972 October 13 (Box 255, Folder 6-11)
- "Coronary Arteriography", 14:21, 1972 October 13 (Box 255, Folder 12-14)
- "Iron Fortification of Foods", 14:22, 1972 October 27 (Box 256, Folder 1-4)
- "Corticosteroids, Topical - Flurandrenolide Tape", 14:22, 1972 October 27 (Box 256, Folder 5-11)
- "Copper in Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices", 14:22, 1972 October 27 (Box 256, Folder 12-15)
- "Moniliasis: Candicidin for Vaginal Candidiasis", 14:23, 1972 November 10 (Box 257, Folder 1-5)
- "Antimicrobial Drugs for Anaerobic Bacterial Infections", 14:23, 1972 November 10 (Box 257, Folder 6-8)
- "Clorazepate (Tranxene) - Another Benzodiazepine", 14:23, 1972 November 10 (Box 257, Folder 9-11, Box 258, Folder 1-2)
- "Blood Transfusions", 14:24, 1972 November 24 (Box 258, Folder 3-8)
- "Anti-Anxiety Drugs in Organic and Functional Syndromes", 14:25, 1972 December 8 (Box 258, Folder 9, Box 259, Folder 1-5)
- "Drugs in Pregnancy", 14:25, 1972 December 8 (Box 259, Folder 6-9)
- "Lypressin (Diaped) and Other Drugs for Diabetes Insipidus", 14:26, 1972 December 22 (Box 259, Folder 10, Box 260, Folder 1-4)
- "The Dalkon Shield Intrauterine Device", 14:26, 1972 December 22 (Box 260, Folder 5-9)
- "Aminopyrine - Dipyrone and aminopyrine - for relief of fever", 15:1, 1973 January 5 (Box 261, Folder 1-7)
- "Skin Diseases, Therapy - Tretinoin (Retinoic Acid) in Acne", 15:1, 1973 January 5 (Box 261, Folder 8-13)
- "Hexachlorophene in the Nursery" 15:1, 1973 January 5 (Box 261, Folder 14-15)
- "Estrogens - Estrogens and the Menopausal Patient", 15:2, 1973 January 19 (Box 261, Folder 16-17, Box 262, Folder 1-2)
- Emergency Care Research Institute, 15:2, 1973 January 19 (Box 262, Folder 3)
- "Tetracylines - Injectable Doxycycline" Consultants, 15:2, 1973 January 19 (Box 262, Folder 4-8)
- "A Note on Treatment for Cryptococcal Meningitis" 15:2, 1973 January 19 (Box 262, Folder 9, Box 263, Folder 1)
- "Special Publications: Reference Handbook, January 1973", 1973 January (Box 263, Folder 2-7)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - The Therapy in the Treatment of Malignancy", 15:3, 1973 February 2 (Box 264, Folder 1-3)
- "Cancer - Surgical Treatment of Early Breast", 15:4, 1973 February 16 (Box 264, Folder 4-7)
- "Anemia - New Treatments for Sickle Cell Disease", 15:4, 1973 February 16 (Box 265, Folder 1-5)
- "Parkinson's Disease, Levodopa - Levodopa and Related Drugs", 15:5, 1973 March 2 (Box 265, Folder 6-8, Box 266, Folder 1-6)
- "Adverse Systemic Effects from Topical Eye Drugs", 15:5, 1973 March 2 (Box 266, Folder 7-10)
- "Clindamycin - Clindamycin", 15:6, 1973 March 16 (Box 266, Folder 11-12, Box 267, Folder 1-5)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Megestrol Acetate (Megace) and Other Progestins in Advanced Endometrial Carcinoma", 15:6, 1973 March 16 (Box 267, Folder 6-12)
- "Promotion of Drugs in Latin America", 15:6, 1973 March 16 (Box 268, Folder 1-3)
- "Penicillins, New (Carbenicillin) - Oral Carbenicillin", 15:7, 1973 March 30 (Box 268, Folder 4-10)
- "Nutrition and Diet - Vegetarian Diets", 15:7, 1973 March 30 (Box 268, Folder 11-13)
- "Narcotics - The Choice and Dosage of Narcotic Analgesics", 15:7, 1973 March 30 (Box 269, Folder 1-2)
- "Obesity - Fenfluramine - Another Appetite Suppressant", 15:8, 1973 April 13 (Box 269, Folder 3-7)
- "Heparin - Low-Dose Heparin Prophylaxis of Deep Vein Thrombosis", 15:8, 1973 April 13 (Box 269, Folder 8-11)
- "Analgesics - Alka-Seltzer", 15:8, 1973 April 13 (Box 269, Folder 12-16, Box 270, Folder 1-2)
- "Lipids, Drug Reduction (Clofibrate) - Clofibrate for Prevention of Myocardial Infarction", 15:9, 1973 April 27 (Box 270, Folder 3-8, Box 271, Folder 1-8)
- "Tetanus - Prophylaxis and Treatment of Tetanus and Other Clostridial Wound Infection", 15:9, 1973 April 27 (Box 271, Folder 9-10, Box 272, Folder 1-2)
- "Phenylbutazone - Phenylbutazone and Osyphenbutozone", 15:9, 1973 April 27 (Box 272, Folder 3-8)
- "Obesity - Dr. Atkins' Diet Revolution", 15:10, 1973 May 11 (Box 272, Folder 9-13)
- "Penicillins - Oral Penicillins", 15:10, 1973 May 11 (Box 272, Folder 14-17, Box 273, Folder 1-3)
- "Contraceptives, Oral - Norethindrone - the 'Minipill'", 15:11, 1973 May 25 (Box 273, Folder 4-9)
- "Addiction - Treatment of Neonatal Withdrawal Syndrome", 15:11, 1973 May 25 (Box 273, Folder 10-16)
- "Advice to Patients on Drugs Purchased While Traveling Abroad", 15:11, 1973 May 25 (Box 274, Folder 1-2)
- "Propranolol - New Uses", 15:12, 1973 June 8 (Box 274, Folder 3-8)
- "Gentamicin for Neonatal Sepsis", 15:12, 1973 June 8 (Box 274, Folder 9-13)
- "Diazoxide (Hyperstat) ", 15:13, 1973 June 22 (Box 275, Folder 1-5)
- "Treatment of Allergenic Thinitis with Injections of Allergenic Extracts", 15:13, 1973 June 22 (Box 275, Folder 6-10)
- "Diazepam as a Muscle Relaxant", 15:14, 1973 July 6 (Box 275, Folder 11, Box 276, Folder 1-4)
- "Diethylstilbestrol as a "Morning-After" Contraceptive", 15:14, 1973 July 6 (Box 276, Folder 5-8)
- "U-100 Insulin", 15:14, 1973 July 6 (Box 276, Folder 9-12)
- "Dextropoxyphene - Darvocet-N", 15:15, 1973 July 20 (Box 277, Folder 1-7)
- "Vitamin 'Remedies' - Lipotropic Products", 15:15, 1973 July 20 (Box 277, Folder 8-13)
- "Cyclophosphamide and Sterility", 15:15, 1973 July 20 (Box 277, Folder 14-19)
- "Sulfamethoxazole - Trimethoprim (Co-Trimoxazole) ", 15:16, 1973 August 3 (Box 277, Folder 20-26)
- "Pregnancy (Nutrition) - Nutrition in Pregnancy", 15:16, 1973 August 3 (Box 278, Folder 1-5)
- "Fungal Infection - Haloprogin for Tinea" 15:17, 1973 August 17 (Box 278, Folder 6-11)
- "Thyroid (Hormones) - Selection of Thyroid Hormone Products", 15:17, 1973 August 17 (Box 278, Folder 12-13, Box 279, Folder 1-4)
- "Preanesthetic Medication - Medication before Anesthesia", 15:17, 1973 August 17 (Box 279, Folder 5-10)
- "Infection - Diseases from Pets", 15:18, 1973 August 31 (Box 279, Folder 11-16, Box 280, Folder 1)
- "Cancer Tests - The Gravlee Jet Washer", 15:18, 1973 August 31 (Box 280, Folder 2-3)
- "Elastic Stocking for Prevention of Postoperative Emboli", 15:18, 1973 August 31 (Box 280, Folder 4-7)
- "Feminins and Other Vitamin-Mineral Supplements for Women Taking Oral Contraceptives" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 15:20, 1973 September 28 (Box 280, Folder 8-11, Box 281, Folder 1)
- "Cholera: Advice for Travelers" Consultants, 15:20, 1973 September 28 (Box 281, Folder 2-3)
- "Muscle Relaxants - Pancuronium", 15:20, 1973 September 28 (Box 281, Folder 4-8)
- "Sulfamethoxazole-Trimethorpim: Bactrim and Septra", 15:21, 1973 October 12 (Box 281, Folder 9-12)
- "Aerosols for Colds", 15:21, 1973 October 12 (Box 281, Folder 13-16, Box 282, Folder 1-2)
- "Cho-Free for Diarrhea in Infants", 15:21, 1973 October 12 (Box 282, Folder 3-8)
- "New Influenza Vaccines", 15:22, 15:24, 1973 October 26; 1973 November 23 (Box 282, Folder 9-13)
- "Drugs for Staphylococcal Infections", 15:23, 1973 November 9 (Box 283, Folder 1-3)
- "Calusterone for Breast Cancer", 15:23, 1973 November 9 (Box 283, Folder 4-8)
- "Carbamazepine (Tegretol) - Trigeminal Neuralgia and Other Uses" 15:23, 1973 November 9 (Box 283, Folder 9-10)
- "Digitalis: Digoxin Tablets", 15:24, 1973 November 23 (Box 284, Folder 1-5)
- "Laxatives and Dietary Fiber", 15:24, 1973 November 23 (Box 284, Folder 6-12)
- "Topical Neomycin", 15:25, 1973 December 7 (Box 285, Folder 1-6)
- "Bleomycin - A New Anticancer Drug", 15:25, 1973 December 7 (Box 285, Folder 7-9, Box 286, Folder 1-2)
- "Urea and Other Agents in Treatment of Dry Skin", 15:25, 1973 December 7 (Box 286, Folder 3-7)
- "Nicotinic Acid in the Treatment of Schizophrenia", 15:26, 1973 December 21 (Box 286, Folder 8-11)
- "Parenteral Administration - Control of Infections from Intravenous Infusions", 15:26, 1973 December 21 (Box 286, Folder 12-13, Box 287, Folder 1-2)
- "Chronic Pulmonary Insufficiency" Never Published, 1973 (Box 287, Folder 3-6)
- "Cephalosporins", 16:1, 1974 January 4 (Box 288, Folder 1-7)
- "Enteric-Coated Potassium", 16:1, 1974 January 4 (Box 288, Folder 8-12)
- "Rho (D) Immune Globulin (Human) ", 16:1, 1974 January 4 (Box 288, Folder 13-14, Box 289, Folder 1-4)
- "Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy - Dosage Article", Special Publication, 1974 January (Box 289, Folder 5-12, Box 290, Folder 1-2)
- "Urinalysis: Microstix and Other Office Tests for Detection of Urinary Tract Infection", 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 290, Folder 3-9)
- "New Developments in Pharmacology of Vitamin D", 16:3, 1974 February 1 (Box 290, Folder 10-16)
- "Anticoagulants in Myocardial Infarction", 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 291, Folder 1-7)
- "Interruption of a Drug Regimen before Anesthesia", 16:4, 1974 February 15 (Box 291, Folder 8-13)
- "Ergotamine and Preparations: Hydergine for Cerebral Arteriosclerosis", 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 1-7)
- "Imipramine for Enuresis", 16:5, 1974 March 1 (Box 292, Folder 8-14)
- "Lactation: Drugs in Breast Milk", 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 1-4)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Dacarbazine for Malignant Melanoma" Basic Source Checklist, 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 5-8)
- "Effects of Systemic Drugs with Anticholinergic Properties on Glaucoma", 16:6, 1974 March 15 (Box 293, Folder 9-13)
- "Haemophilus Influenzae Meningitis Resistant to Ampicillin" Consultants, M. L. Drafts, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 293, Folder 14)
- "Haemophilus Influenzae Meningitis Resistant to Ampicillin" Reprints, 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 293, Folder 15)
- "Imipramine: Tofranil-PM and Antidepressant Therapy", 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 1-7)
- "Drug Treatment of Ulcerative Colitis", 16:7, 1974 March 29 (Box 294, Folder 8-14, Box 295, Folder 1-3)
- "Lipids, Drug Reductions: Cholestyramine for Elevated Serum Cholesterol", 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 295, Folder 4-8)
- "Drugs, Injurious Effects (Collagen): Drug-Induced Lupus Syndrome", 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 295, Folder 9-12, Box 296, Folder 1-4)
- "Allergies: Allergic Reaction to Pets", 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 296, Folder 5-7)
- "Allergies: Allergic Reaction to Pets" Original Manuscript, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 296, Folder 6)
- "Allergies: Allergic Reaction to Pets" Reprints, 16:8, 1974 April 12 (Box 296, Folder 7)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents", 16:9, 1974 April 26 (Box 296, Folder 8-12, Box 297, Folder 1)
- "FDA Approval of Medroxyprogesterone for Contraception" Reprints, 16:11, Article in response to "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents", 1974 May 24 (Box 297, Folder 2-3)
- "Topical and Systemic Contraceptive Agents" Advertising Package Inserts, 16:9, 1974 April 26 (Box 297, Folder 4)
- "Streptozyme Test", 16:10., 1974 May 10 (Box 297, Folder 5-10)
- "Anesthetics: Dangers of Innovar", 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 297, Folder 11-12, Box 298, Folder 1-5)
- "Burns: Silver Sulfadiazine", 16:10, 1974 May 10 (Box 298, Folder 6-13)
- "Asthma, Drugs for: Metaproterenol", 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 1-4)
- "Obesity: Intestinal Surgery for Obesity", 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 5-10)
- "Antiemetics: Drugs for Relief of Nausea and Vomiting", 16:11, 1974 May 24 (Box 299, Folder 11-16, Box 300, Folder 1-3)
- "Penicillin, New: Amoxicillin", 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 300, Folder 4-11)
- "Gels and Other Topical Corticosteroids", 16:12, 1974 June 7 (Box 300, Folder 12-13, Box 301, Folder 1-5)
- "Cephapirim", 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 6-10)
- "Obesity, Drugs for: Two New Appetite Suppressants", 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 301, Folder 11-15, Box 302, Folder 1-2)
- "Fluoride for the Prevention of Dental Cavities", 16:13, 1974 June 21 (Box 302, Folder 3-10)
- "Is All Aspirin Alike? ", 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 1-8)
- "Sunburns: Sunscreens", 16:14, 1974 July 5 (Box 303, Folder 9-12)
- "Dantrolene Sodium for Treatment of Spasticity", 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 303, Folder 13-14, Box 304, Folder 1-4)
- "Parasitic Infections: Mycanthone for Schistosomiasis", 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 5-10)
- "Insect Bites and Stings: Systemic Reactions to Hymenoptera Stings", 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 304, Folder 11, Box 305, Folder 1-4)
- "Travelers' Warning: Dipyrone in Over-the-Counter Drugs", 16:15, 1974 July 19 (Box 305, Folder 5-8)
- "Hypertension Therapy: Drugs for Hypertension", 16:16, 1974 August 2 (Box 305, Folder 9-13, Box 306, Folder 1-2)
- "The Treatment of Hodgkin's Disease", 16:17, 1974 August 16 (Box 306, Folder 3-7)
- "Diarrhea: Warning on Diiodohydroxyquin", 16:17, 1974 August 16 (Box 306, Folder 8-10)
- "Colitis Associated with Clindamycin", 16:18, 1974 August 30 (Box 306, Folder 11, Box 307, Folder 1-6)
- "Immunization (Vaccines): Meningococcal Vaccine", 16:18, 1974 August 30 (Box 307, Folder 7-10)
- "Additives (Food, Drug and Cosmetic): Nitrates and Nitrites in Food"; 16:18, 1974 August 30 (Box 307, Folder 11-12, Box 308, Folder 1-2)
- "Diuretics: Metolazone" Consultants, 16:19, 1974 September 13 (Box 308, Folder 3-9)
- "Calcium: Intravenous Phosphate Solution for Treatment of Hypercalcemia", 16:19, 1974 September 13 (Box 308, Folder 10-12, Box 309, Folder 1-5)
- "Penicillins, New (Ampicillin): Oral Ampicillin", 16:19, 1974 September 13 (Box 309, Folder 6-10)
- "New Influenza Vaccine for 1974-1975", 16:20, 1974 September 27 (Box 309, Folder 11-14)
- "Streptoccocal Infections: Management of Contacts of Patients with Streptoccocal Pharyngitis", 16:20, 1974 September 27 (Box 309, Folder 15-19)
- "Isosorbide", 16:20, 1974 September 27 (Box 310, Folder 1-7)
- "Vitamins, C: Vitamin C and the Common Cold", 16:21, 1974 October 11 (Box 310, Folder 8-14)
- "Penicillins: Benzathine Penicillin G for Intramuscular Injection", 16:21, 1974 October 11 (Box 310, Folder 15, Box 311, Folder 1-4)
- "Prostaglandins: Prostin F2 Alpha for Second Trimester Abortion", 16:22, 1974 October 25 (Box 311, Folder 5-9)
- "Diabetes, Therapy: Oral Hypoglycemic Agents", 16:22, 1974 October 25 (Box 311, Folder 10-12, Box 312, Folder 1-4)
- "Drug Interaction: Interactions of Alcohol with Other Drugs", 16:22, 1974 October 25 (Box 312, Folder 5-9)
- "Penicillins, New (Ampicillin): What To Do When Your Hospital Runs Out Of Parenteral Ampicillin", 16:23, 1974 November 8 (Box 312, Folder 10-12)
- "Cancer Tests: Carcinoembryonic Antigen (CEA) Assay", 16:23, 1974 November 8 (Box 312, Folder 13-15, Box 313, Folder 1-2)
- "Diazepam (Valium) in Hypertension", 16:23, 1974 November 8 (Box 313, Folder 3-7)
- "Miconazole - A New Topical Antifungal Drug", 16:24, 1974 November 22 (Box 313, Folder 8-14)
- "Cephalosporins: Cephradine - A New Oral Cephalosporin Antibiotic", 16:24, 1974 November 22 (Box 313, Folder 15, Box 314, Folder 1-6)
- "Arrhythmias: Treatment of Cardiac Arrhythmias" Adverse Effects, 16:25, 1974 December 6 (Box 314, Folder 7-11, Box 315, Folder 1-7)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): Ibuprofen (Motrin) - A New Drug for Arthritis", 16:26, 1974 December 20 (Box 315, Folder 8-12, Box 316, Folder 1-2)
- "Methadone Maintenance", 16:26, 1974 December 20 (Box 316, Folder 3-9)
- "Viral Infection (Herpes): Photoactive Dyes for Recurrent Herpes Simplex", 16:26, 1974 December 20 (Box 316, Folder 10, Box 317, Folder 1-6)
- "Depression, Therapy: Antidepressant Drugs", 17:1, 1975 January 3 (Box 317, Folder 7-12)
- "Anemia: Glucose - 6 - Phosphate Dehydrogenase Deficiency", 17:1, 1975 January 3 (Box 318, Folder 1-5)
- "Drug Prices: Cost of Prescription Drugs", 17:2, 1975 January 17 (Box 318, Folder 6-9)
- "Urine Pregnancy Tests", 17:2, 1975 January 17 (Box 318, Folder 10-16)
- "Hemorrhoids: Treatment of Hemorrhoids" Basic Source Checklist, 17:2, 1975 January 17 (Box 318, Folder 17-19, Box 319, Folder 1)
- "Asthma, Drugs for: Oral Theophylline Drugs for Asthma", 17:3, 1975 January 31 (Box 319, Folder 2-7)